<?xml version="1.0"?>

<root available-locales="en_US" default-locale="en_US">
	<static-content language-id="en_US">&lt;p&gt; &lt;u&gt;To add Business Defined Content Type and related metadata:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; Add a new Business Defined Content Type:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; Access the Documents and Media portlet.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the Documents and Media screen select "Manage" then "Document Types".&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the Document Types screen press the "Add" button.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the "New Document Type" screen give your content type a name and optionally a description.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; Add the main metadata for the Business Defined Content Type:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; In the "Main Metadata Fields" section, drag and drop form fields from the palette on the left to the canvas on the right.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Double click on the first field on the canvas on the right side of the screen.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Review all of the field properties in the "Settings" tab on the left side of the screen.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Double click the "Field Label" setting, and enter the text you would like to use as a label for the field.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Continue setting the field labels for the remaining form fields.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; Associate any additional metadata for the Business Defined Content Type:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; In the "Additional Metadata Fields" section select "Select Metadata Set".&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the "Metadata Sets" screen press the "Add" button.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the "New Metadata Sets" screen define the Metadata Set Fields the same way as previously done for the "Main Metadata Fields".&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; On the "New Metadata Sets" screen press the "Save" button to save the Metadata Set.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; On the "New Document Type" screen press the "Save" button to save the Business Defined Content Type.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;u&gt;To add Business Defined Content to the repository:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; Access the Documents and Media portlet.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From the "Documents and Media" screen press the "Add" button, then select your Business Defined Content Type.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; From your Business Defined Content Type screen upload the business defined content and enter any appropriate values in the metadata fields.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Press the "Publish" button.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;u&gt;To view Business Defined Content:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; Add a "Documents and Media Display" portlet to a page.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; You should now be able to see your Business Defined Content Type in the appropriate folder(s).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</static-content>
</root>