<model><model-name>com.liferay.portlet.messageboards.model.MBMessage</model-name><column><column-name>uuid</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[44f2bce8-1dfc-412e-ad8c-b840a151921a]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>messageId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[346317]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>groupId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[10180]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>companyId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[10154]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>userId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[104118]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>userName</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[Rosenda Junkins]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>createDate</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[2012-08-09 04:54:32.663]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>modifiedDate</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[2012-08-09 04:54:32.663]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>classNameId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[0]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>classPK</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[0]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>categoryId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[346315]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>threadId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[346318]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>rootMessageId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[346317]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>parentMessageId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[0]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>subject</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[Norman conquest of England]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>body</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[<p>The <b>Norman conquest of England</b> was the 11th-century invasion and occupation of England by an army of Normans, Bretons and French led by Duke William II of Normandy. William, who defeated Anglo-Saxon King Harold II of England on 14 October 1066, at the Battle of Hastings, was crowned king at London on Christmas Day, 1066. He then consolidated his control and settled many of his followers in England, introducing a number of governmental and societal changes.</p>

<p>William's claim to the English throne derived from his familial relationship with the childless King Edward the Confessor, who may have encouraged William's hopes for the throne. But when Edward died in January 1066, he was succeeded by his brother-in-law Harold, who not only faced challenges from William but also another claim by the Norwegian king, Harald Hardrada. Hardrada invaded northern England in September 1066 and was victorious at the Battle of Fulford before being defeated and killed by King Harold at the Battle of Stamford Bridge on 25 September 1066. William, however, had landed in southern England, and Harold quickly marched south to confront William, leaving many of his forces behind in the north. On 14 October Harold's army confronted William's invaders near Hastings and after an all-day battle, was defeated and Harold was killed.</p>

<p>Although William's main rivals were gone, he still faced a number of rebellions over the following years, and it was not until after 1072 that he was secure on his throne. Native resistance led to a number of the English elite having their lands confiscated, and some went into exile. To control his new kingdom, William gave lands to his followers and built castles throughout the land to command military strongpoints. Other changes included the introduction of Norman French as the language of the noble elite, the court and government, and changes in the composition of the upper classes, as William enfeoffed lands to be held directly of the king. More slowly the conquest eventually changed the agricultural classes and village life: the main immediate change appears to have been the formal elimination of slavery, which may or may not have been linked to the invasion. There was little change in the structure of government, as the the new Norman administrators took over many of the forms of Anglo-Saxon government.</p>]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>format</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[html]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>attachments</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[false]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>anonymous</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[false]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>priority</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[1.0]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>allowPingbacks</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[true]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>answer</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[false]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>status</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[0]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>statusByUserId</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[104118]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>statusByUserName</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[Rosenda Junkins]]></column-value></column><column><column-name>statusDate</column-name><column-value><![CDATA[2012-08-09 04:54:32.663]]></column-value></column></model>